http://prolabscientific.com/Privacy-policy.html

GPI anatomical models
Foam models (K-8)
Educational test papers
Food hygiene test papers (chlorine, QAC, etc.)
Microscopes
Beginner (elementary schools)
Intermediate (high schools)
Advanced (colleges and universities)
Prolab Scientific online catalogue
Safety datasheets (SDS)
0
0 item(s)
Last added items
Subtotal:
$ 0.00
View cart
Checkout
The order subtotal is less than the minimum allowed value ($ 40.00)
Search
0
Privacy policy
Prolab Scientific Ltd. is committed to respecting the privacy of individuals and recognizes the need of people with whom we do business and employees for the appropriate management and protection of any Personal Information that you agree to provide to us. Our Privacy Management Plan includes guidelines on the collection, storage, use and retention of your Personal Information as follows:Collection: The organization collects personal information about individuals (clients, suppliers, employees, etc.) in order to better manage its business. The organization will make all reasonable effort to fully inform such individuals about the planned use/disclosure. The organization will limit the collection and use of personal information to that required for valid business purposes or to comply with legislation.Consent: The organization will make every reasonable effort to obtain your consent before collecting, using, or disclosing your personal information. In each instance we will provide you with a reason statement that outlines: The information we require The purpose(s) for which we are collecting it The approximate length of time we expect to hold your information If you have any questions about the process please contact our Chief Privacy Officer using the contact information listed.Accuracy: The organization will make every reasonable effort to ensure that the personal information it collects and uses is accurate and complete. Individuals providing personal information will have the opportunity to review and correct their personal information, and on written request by an individual to whom the information relates, the organization will modify the information as required.Storage: The organization will store personal information using hard copy and/or electronic means in such a way as to prevent unauthorized collection, access, use disclosure or disposal of the personal information.Retention: The organization will establish a retention period for all personal information collected. This period may be related to legislation other than Personal Information Protection and Electronic Document Act or PIPEDA (Employment Standards for example).Disclosure: the organization will not disclose personal information unnecessarily to employees or any third party, unless the affected individuals consent.Access: The organization promotes an individual’s right of access to personal information about themselves. The organization will provide access to information upon request. Access will be provided according to established procedures.
Contact us
2213 le Chatelier, Laval, QC, CA, H7L 5B3
1-800-556-5226
Send a message
Quick links
Purchase order form
Credit application form
Sitemap
Safety data sheets (SDS)
Form W-8BEN
© 1996 - 2020 Prolab Scientific Ltd.. All rights reserved.
